<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 02:33:31 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DEVELOPMENTAL INTEGRITY</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/developmental-integrity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 02:33:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/developmental-integrity/</guid>
      <description>Currently, the projects for the site are on a hault. Since doing this, I have gained a tremendous amount of dicipline in figuring out this static site generator. There was pain, patience, and continous encouragement for the success of this site. Reasons for not continuing in advacements into this plan was due to the lack of experience with other themes and what entailed with them like CMS(Content Management System) or using StartBootstrap(themes to use for site content presentation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally!! A Successful Hugo Deployment</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 01:38:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Trying to get this site rendered successfully was not an easy feat. Several changes were made to get this up and running. This is my first successful commit to deploying a site through render by github repository initialization. it took me a week and a few days. This was not some lateral condition of success, in fact several attempts to get this fully rendered and deployed. As someone starting out in the field with no instructor, consistency directed with the harness of drive to understand, some things must be understood.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
